(GROWLING)
(GUNSHOTS)
(HULK ROARING)
(HEART BEATING)
(EXHALES)
(DOG BARKING)
Is it ready?
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Hey! That's a great punch.
Fear no good.
So emotion and control.
(BOTH BREATHING RAPIDLY)
Breathe. Breathe.
(WATCH BEEPING)
(BREATHING RAPIDLY)
(WATCH BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Wait.
(BEEPING SLOWS)
(ALARM BUZZING)
(MACHINES WHIRRING)
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Okay.
I can make it
work for a while,
but you need...
(MEN SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Okay. Okay.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(EXCLAIMS)
Shut that off!
Turn it off!
Watch out!
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(ALARM BUZZING)
Okay!
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(CHATTERING)
Hmm?
That's not right.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(MEN SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Oh, you.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
You see that? See that?
My ticket out of here.
(SIGHS)
Damn it!
(MEN SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Here's something
a bit more interesting.
It's a possible
gamma sickness.
Milwaukee.
A man drank
one of those
guarana sodas.
Guess it had
a little more kick
than he was looking for.
Wow.
Where was it bottled?
Porto Verde, Brazil.
Have our people
look for a white man
at the bottling plant.
Tell them no contact!
If he even sees them,
he's gone!
I got you who I could.
Short notice,
but they're all quality.
And I pulled you one ace.
Emil Blonsky.
Born in Russia,
raised in England.
And on loan to SOCOM
from the Royal Marines.
GENERAL: I know
you cashed in some chips
for this, Joe.
Glad I could help.
Just make it good.
SPARR: This is the target
and the location.
Snatch and grab,
live capture.
You'll have your dart clips
and suppression ordnance,
but live fire is
for backup only.
We got local out there,
but we want it tight
and quiet.
Is he a fighter?
Your target is a fugitive
from the US government
who stole military secrets.
He is also implicated
in the deaths
of two scientists,
a military officer, an Idaho
state trooper and possibly
two Canadian hunters.
So don't wait to see
if he's a fighter!
Tranq him
and bring him back.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
Oh, come on.
(DOG BARKING)
(WHINING)
(TRACKER BEEPING)
Camera.
(TRACKER BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Here we go.
Get rid of the damn dog.
Take him!
Target's on the move.
(GUN FIRES)
(SCREAMS)
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Where is he?
He's on the ground.
Let's go!
COMMANDO: Go!
Move, move!
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
Go, go, go!
Go! Go!
COMMANDO:
Clear everyone out!
Do not lose him!
Oh! No!
(WATCH BEEPING)
(WATCH BEEPING RAPIDLY)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(WATCH BEEPING SLOWS)
Get around behind him!
Target moving past
mobile unit 0-9-0.
Oh, no.
You got to be
kidding me.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(GATE RATTLING)
(METAL CLANKING)
GENERAL ON RADIO:
Where is he?
Target acquired.
(WATCH BEEPING RAPIDLY)
MAN: Gringo!
(MAN SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(WHISPERING)
Let's go.
(MEN SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
No!
Please! No!
Not the computer!
Gimme that! No!
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
You bad angry, G?
I very bad angry.
(GRUNTS)
BRUCE: Oh, no.
You don't understand!
Something really bad is
about to happen here!
(SILENCED GUNSHOT)
(WATCH BEEPING RAPIDLY)
(WHISPERING)
Anybody else seeing this?
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(ROARING)
COMMANDO 1: We've got
a bogey of some kind.
Please advise.
That is the target!
Use every tranq you've got!
Do it now!
(GUNS FIRING)
Go live! Go live! Go live!
COMMANDO 1: Move!
COMMANDO 2:
Get out of the way!
No!
(GROWLING)
(GUNS FIRING)
(ALARM BUZZING)
COMMANDO 2:
It's behind us!
Move! Move!
COMMANDO 1:
Get him!
Shoot!
HULK: Leave me alone.
(GROWLING)
No! No!
(HULK ROARING)
I knew something was different
before I got the shot off.
He had it on him
when he bolted.
Is that a girlfriend?
She helps him, maybe?
She is no longer a factor.
We closed that door
to him a long time ago.
He's alone.
He wants to be alone.
But see if he's been
talking to anybody.
Forgive me, sir?
Doesn't anybody want
to talk about what went down
in there? 'Cause...
He didn't lose us.
And he was
not alone, sir.
We had him.
And then something
hit us, something...
Something big hit us!
It threw a forklift truck
like it was a softball!
It was the most
powerful thing
I've ever seen.
Well, it's gone.
Well, if Banner
knows what it is,
I'm gonna track him down,
I'm gonna put my foot
on his throat
and I'm gonna...
That was Banner.
It
was Banner.
You have to explain
that statement, sir.
No, I don't.
You've done a good job.
Pack up and get
our men on a plane.
We're going home.
Wait.
Please.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Where am I?
(MAN SPEAKING SPANISH)
(BRUCE SPEAKING SPANISH)
I've run into
bad situations on
crap missions before.
I've seen
good men
go down
purely because someone
didn't let us know
what we were walking into.
I've moved on to the next one,
because that's what we do,
right?
I mean, that's the job.
But this?
This is a whole
new level of weird.
And I don't feel inclined
to step away from it.
So if you're taking
another crack at him,
I want in.
And, with respect, you should
be looking for a team that's
prepped and ready to fight,
because if that thing
shows up again,
you're gonna have a lot
of professional tough guys
pissing in their pants.
Sir.
(HENS CLUCKING)
(DOG BARKING)
(COINS JINGLING)
Tienes más stretchy?
Yeah. Perfecto.
(MOTORCYCLE PASSING)
Let me emphasize
that what I'm about
to share with you
is tremendously sensitive,
both to me personally
and the Army.
You're aware that
we've got an Infantry
Weapons Development program.
Well, in WWII,
they initiated
a subprogram
for Bio-Tech
Force Enhancement.
Yeah, Super Soldier.
Yes.
An oversimplification,
but yes.
And I dusted it off,
got 'em doing serious
work again, bold work.
Across the hall,
they were trying
to arm you better.
We were tryin'
to make you better.
Banner's work was
very early phase.
It wasn't even
weapons application.
He thought he was working
on radiation resistance.
I would never have told him
what the project really was.
But he was so sure
of what he was onto,
that he tested it
on himself.
And something went
very wrong.
Or it went very right.
As far as I'm concerned,
that man's whole body is
the property of the US Army.
You said he wasn't working
on weapons, right?
No.
But you were.
You were, weren't you?
You were trying
other things.
One serum we developed
was very promising.
So why did he run?
He's a scientist.
He is not one of us.
Blonsky, how old
are you? 45?
39.
It takes a toll,
doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
So get out
of the trenches.
You should be
a Colonel by now,
with your record.
No, I'm a fighter.
I'll be one for
as long as I can.
You know, if I could
take what I know now,
put it in the body
I had ten years ago,
that would be someone
I wouldn't want to fight.
I could probably arrange
something like that.
(DOOR OPENING)
Take care, kids.
Stan, I give you my word,
whatever you've heard
about me, it's not true.
Oh, I know it.
I always knew it.
I mean, you know
how I felt
about you two.
Have you talked to her?
No.
She doesn't know
that I'm here.
She's with somebody?
Yeah, he's a head shrink.
They say he's one of the best.
But a really nice guy.
Good. That's good.
Bruce, what can I do
to help you?
I could use a bed
for a few nights.
You can have
the spare room upstairs.
That'd be so great.
There is one other thing.
Excuse me. Pardon me.
(BICYCLE BELL RINGING)
Coming through.
Hey, pal.
I got a delivery
on five.
I don't think
there's anybody
up there.
Oh, man.
I'm gonna catch hell
if I don't collect.
You got to let me try.
I'll tell you what.
I got an extra medium.
Take it on the house.
You are the man.
God bless you, brother.
All right.
(MACHINE BEEPING)
Okay.
We're pretty well closed
here, folks. I'm sorry.
Oh, come on, Stan.
It's Friday night.
Oh, kids.
I got nothing
but marinara now.
Oh, I got to have
a Mister Pink, please.
She worked through
dinner again, of course.
Stan?
(LAUGHING) And he...
I go, "So, yeah, I mean,
where were you?
"I can't... I don't know
where you were, Cecil."
And he goes,
"Not where you been at."
I thought,
"Oh, my God."
I just felt so awful.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(SOFTLY) Bruce?
Betty? What's going on?
Betty...
Just tell me
if I saw
what I think I saw.
I don't know what to say.
Please, just
tell me the truth.
Don't go.
(SIGHING)
I want you
to come with me now.
Please. Come with me.
Please.
(GARAGE DOOR CLOSING)
BETTY: It's our data.
I got in there
before they carted it
all away.
I hoped somewhere
that it might tell us
something someday.
Does the General know
that you have this?
No, I don't think so.
I haven't spoken to him
in a couple of years.
You have to be sure.
Bruce, I don't understand
why we can't just go in there
together and talk to him.
He told me
what he wanted to do.
He wants it out of me.
He wants to dissect it
so that he can replicate it.
He wants to
make it a weapon.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Hi.
I thought you
might want to...
Thanks.
Listen, I should leave early,
as early as I can.
Really?
You can't
stay at all?
I want to,
but it's just not safe
for me to be here.
If I could borrow
some cash...
Of course.
I need to take a bus.
Well, at least
let me walk you
to the station.
Okay.
You have
everything you need?
Yeah.
I...
What?
Good night.
I hope you get
some rest.
We're giving you
a very low dose only.
I need you sharp
out there and disciplined.
First sign
of any side effect,
we stop and you're off team
until you straighten out.
Agreed?
Agreed.
You'll get two
separate infusions.
One into the deep muscle,
one into the bone marrow
centers.
The bone ones
are going to hurt.
(GRUNTS)
Is everything okay?
I think so.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Come here.
(CHUCKLES)
I just wanna do this.
Oh.
It's better like that.
Yeah?
It feels too tight, huh?
Yeah, a little.
Okay.
What?
They're here.
Betty, look at me,
look at me!
Bruce!
You have to go far away
from me as you can!
Don't argue with me,
just go. Go!
Bruce!
(CAR ALARM BEEPING)
Damn it! We'd have
had snipers on target
in three more minutes.
I wanna know
who jumped the gun.
He's heading 2-7-0.
Blonsky! Not yet!
Sir.
Look alive.
This could get interesting.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
I got him!
Stop! Stop!
I know you're in there!
General, please!
Sir?
Dad!
Dad, please don't do this.
You can't see this clearly.
Now, get inside.
There he is!
SOLDIER 1 ON RADIO:
Target is in the overpass.
We have a visual.
Do not engage!
Repeat, do not engage!
SOLDIER 2:
He's locked in.
Put two canisters
in there with him.
Fire!
Get her back here!
(GROANING)
Now she'll see.
(ROARING)
Alpha team?
Let him have all of it.
SOLDIER 2:
Come on, light him up!
Where are the fifty cals?
Move your asses!
Oh, my God!
Blonsky, now you're up!
Sir?
Cover me.
(FIRES)
(GROWLING)
Remember me?
My God, he's doing it.
Move him toward
the cannons!
Move!
SOLDIER 2:
Hold your position!
Do it now!
(HIGH-PITCHED BUZZING)
Please, please,
please, no!
Please, please, please!
Get her back!
You're killing him!
Stop! Get off of me!
(DISTORTED) Bruce!
(DISTORTED)
Bruce! Bruce!
Where's the gunship?
(GROWLS)
Is that it?
Blonsky, pull back now.
Pull back!
Is that all you got?
Fall back!
SOLDIER 3: Fall back!
Let's go, let's go!
GENERAL: Find cover!
Betty!
Fire, goddamn it!
Bruce?
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
Stop firing!
No!
You did the right thing,
calling us.
I need to know
where they're going.
She'll be in incredible danger
as long as she's with him.
From who?
He protected her.
You almost killed her.
I give you my word,
her safety is my main
concern at this point.
You know, it's a point
of professional pride with me
that I can always tell
when somebody's lying.
And you are.
I don't know
where he's going.
I know she'll help him,
if she can.
Then she's aiding
a fugitive.
And I can't help
either one of them.
I used to wonder
why she never
talked about you.
Now I know!
Where does she meet
these guys?
(SIREN WAILS)
(SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
Bruce?
Bruce.
(ROARING)
It's okay. It's okay.
Come here.
Come this way.
Watch your head.
Okay.
We're okay.
It's okay.
It's just the rain.
GENERAL:
Will he ever
walk again?
Most of the bones
in his body look like
crushed gravel right now.
I will say this for him.
He's got a heart
like a machine.
Never seen anything like it,
outside of a racehorse.
Here.
Okay.
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
(BRUCE VOMITING)
Bruce?
Oh, hi.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, actually,
I feel a lot better.
Good.
I just had to get
my data back.
You ate it?
Well, you know,
the circumstances called
for a little improvisation.
Wow.
Okay, so they didn't
have a great selection,
but I got you
some options.
First thing's first.
(BETTY CHUCKLES)
BRUCE: Oh, you're kidding me.
What?
No.
They were the stretchiest
pair they had.
I'll take my chances.
FEMALE REPORTER:
Rumors continue to swirl
about a violent clash
between forces of
the US military and
an unknown adversary
on the campus
of Culver University
earlier today.
Sophomores Jack McGee
and Jim Wilson witnessed
some of the battle.
JIM: It was so big.
It was like this huge,
like, hulk!
Yeah.
FEMALE REPORTER:
McGee, who happens to be a
reporter for the campus paper,
captured this
on his cell phone.
Further search for
the mysterious "hulk"
was postponed by powerful
thunderstorms in the Smoky
Mountain National Forest.
Not too short back there.
(CHUCKLES) I have
done this before,
you know.
I don't know how
you've done this on
your own for all this time.
With clippers, usually.
(GIGGLING)
(WATCH BEEPING)
(WATCH BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Wait, wait, wait. Wait.
What? What?
We can't do this.
It's okay. I want to.
No.
I can't.
(WATCH BEEPING SLOWS)
I can't get too excited.
(BEEPING STOPS)
Not even a little excited?
(SIGHING)
It's okay.
Sir, it's Blonsky.
Has anyone found out
if he has next of kin
or family?
Ask him yourself.
Sir?
Good to see you
back on your feet,
soldier.
Thank you, sir.
How do you feel?
Pissed off and ready
for round three.
Basically, we can't use
any of this, because
they can track all of it.
Well, my lip gloss?
Can they track that?
No. You can take
your lip gloss.
Thank you.
Well, I need
my glasses.
Well, you can take
your glasses
and your watch, okay?
Okay.
We can use most of it.
We just can't use the credit
cards, the ID or the phone.
Don't even turn that on.
Okay.
And we'll take
the cash, obviously.
How will we get
where we need to go on $40
and no credit cards?
Well, we could sell this.
No. No, that's the only thing
you have left from her. No.
Well, we'll have to
try and get it back.
SPARR: Federal is already
monitoring phones, plastic
and Dr. Ross's web accounts,
and local PD have
been placed on alert.
They'll pop up somewhere
and when they do,
it comes straight to us.
GENERAL:
They're not gonna
just pop up.
He made it five years
and got across borders
without making any mistakes.
He's not gonna use
a damn credit card now.
If he was trying to escape,
he'd be long gone.
He's not trying
to escape this time.
He's looking for help
and that's how
we're gonna get him.
We know what they're after
and we know he's been
talking to somebody.
You all have copies
of the correspondence.
The aliases
Mr. Green and Mr. Blue
have been added to the
SHIELD Operations Database.
If he comes up for air,
we'll be waiting.
If he makes a peep,
we'll hear him.
And when he slips up,
we'll be ready.
Hey.
Smile.
(CAMERA BEEPS)
What is it like?
When it happens,
what do you experience?
Remember those experiments
we volunteered for at Harvard?
Those induced
hallucinations?
It's a lot like that,
just a thousand
times amplified.
It's like someone's poured
a liter of acid into my brain.
Do you remember
anything?
Just fragments. Images.
There's too much noise.
I can never derive
anything out of it.
But then it's still
you inside it.
No. No, it's not.
I don't know.
In the cave, I really
felt like it knew me.
Maybe your mind
is in there,
it's just overcharged
and can't process
what's happening.
I don't want to control it.
I want to get rid of it.
Are you ready?
Let's even the playing
field a little.
Gentlemen.
(CAR HONKING)
BETTY: Bruce, wake up.
There's something going on.
We got to go.
Walk toward the back.
Just don't move too fast.
MAN: All right. Come.
BETTY: It is
a long way uptown.
I think the subway's
probably quickest.
Me in a metal tube,
deep underground,
with hundreds of people
in the most aggressive
city in the world?
Right. Let's get a cab.
CAB DRIVER: Come on, now!
Let's go! You're too slow!
You drive like a woman!
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING
ON RADIO)
Very nice. You see her?
Oh, my.
Very pretty.
Watch out, you goat!
(WATCH BEEPING)
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
Are you out of your mind?
What is wrong with you?
What's the matter, baby?
You don't like
a good ride?
(BETTY GROWLING)
Asshole!
(GRUNTS)
You know, I know
a few techniques
could help you
manage that anger
very effectively.
You zip it.
We're walking.
Okay.
BETTY: Excuse me.
Dr. Sterns?
Yes.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm Elizabeth Ross.
Oh! Dr. Ross!
I have someone
who'd like to meet you.
Okay.
It's Mr. Blue, isn't it?
Mr. Green?
I got to tell you,
I've been wondering
if you were even real.
And if you were,
what would it look like?
A person with that much
power lurking in him.
Nothing could have
surprised me more
than this unassuming man
shaking my hand.
But, look. We're not
strolling into the park
for a picnic, here.
Even if everything
goes perfectly,
if we induce an episode,
if we get the dosage
exactly right,
is that going to be
a lasting cure
or just some antidote
to suppress that
specific flare-up?
(SNAPPING FINGERS)
I don't know.
What I'm saying is that
if we overshoot this by
even the smallest integer
we're dealing
with concentrations
with extraordinary
levels of toxicity.
You mean
it could kill him.
Kill him? Yeah.
I should say so.
You should know that there's
a flip side to this, too.
If we miss on the low side,
if we induce me and it fails,
this will be
very dangerous for you.
(CHUCKLES)
Look. I've always been
more curious than cautious,
and that's served me
pretty well.
So, are we going
to do this?
How you feeling, man?
Like a monster.
(MACHINES WHIRRING)
Okay. On the table.
These will protect you
from yourself if you
have a strong reaction.
You can tell me later
if you thought it was strong.
Oh, come on!
Stupid graduate students.
Okay...
You, you, you.
This will be
a somewhat
novel sensation.
We have begun.
The dialysis machine
will mix the antidote
with your blood.
Except the antidote will only
take hold once we've achieved
a full reaction.
Just relax.
Okay. We are comprehensive.
Here you go.
All right.
We set to pop?
I'd take your hands off him.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Oh, my God!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
Wait, wait!
There's more! Wait!
Now. Okay, now!
STERNS: Wait.
Now, do it! Do it!
(GRUNTS)
Bruce! Bruce,
look at me.
Stay with me.
The antidote, now!
Sterns, do it now!
Bruce, look at me.
Look in my eyes.
Please, look in my eyes.
(MACHINE BEEPING)
Oh, you've got
to be kidding me!
(GROANING)
Bruce.
Oh, my God.
Bruce? Bruce,
can you hear me?
Bruce?
It's okay.
You're okay.
You did it.
He's fine.
This is fantastic.
BETTY: It's over.
Hi.
(POLICE SIREN WAILING)
That was the most
extraordinary thing I have
seen in my entire life!
Okay, you know what?
Stop, please.
We need to go back
and talk about what
just happened in there.
Absolutely. Okay.
The gamma pulse came
from the amygdala.
I think Dr. Ross's primer...
Are you okay?
...lets the cells absorb
the energy temporarily,
and then it abates.
That's why you didn't
die of radiation sickness
years ago!
Now, maybe we've neutralized
those cells permanently,
or maybe we just
suppressed that event.
I'm inclined to think
the latter, but it's hard
to know
because none
of our test subjects
ever survived.
Of course, they weren't
getting the primer!
Wait, wait.
Wait, what did you just say?
They weren't getting
the myostatin primer...
No, no, no.
Test subjects?
What test subjects?
Come with me.
(SIRENS WAILING)
What's the activity level?
Snipers are covering
Alpha sector.
STERNS ON RADIO:
We started on rats and mice,
but it just completely
fried them, so we had
to go bigger.
And we still don't know
which is more toxic,
the gamma or your blood.
What do you mean,
my blood?
Bruce, this is all you.
You didn't send me
much to work with,
so I had to
concentrate it
and make more.
With a little more
trial and error, there's
no end to what we can do!
This is potentially
Olympian!
This gamma technology has
limitless applications.
We'll unlock
hundreds of cures.
We will make humans
impervious to disease!
No, no, we've
got to destroy it.
Wait, what?
All of it.
Tonight. We're
gonna incinerate it.
Is this the whole supply?
What...
We could get
the Nobel for this!
You don't understand
the power of this thing.
It is too dangerous.
It cannot be controlled.
At your discretion, shooter.
STERNS: ...three of us!
This is Promethean fire!
BRUCE: It's just...
SOLDIER ON RADIO:
No shot.
Blonsky's going in.
GENERAL ON RADIO:
Blonsky, stand down.
My daughter's in there!
We have the antidote now.
They don't want the antidote!
They want to make it a weapon!
(SIRENS WAILING)
And if we let it go,
we will never get it back.
You don't know
how powerful this thing is.
I hate the government
just as much as anyone,
but you're being
a little paranoid,
don't you think?
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
(SHRIEKS)
Bruce! Bruce!
BRUCE: Get out.
Where is it?
Come on,
where is it?
(EXCLAIMS)
(WATCH BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Show him to me.
(HEART BEATING SLOWLY)
Blonsky!
SOLDIER: Miss!
Take this.
If you took it from me,
I'm gonna put you in a hole
for the rest of your life.
Betty.
I will never forgive
what you've done to him.
He's a fugitive.
You made him a fugitive
to cover your failures
and to protect your career.
Don't ever speak to me
as your daughter again.
It's only because you're
my daughter that you're
not in handcuffs, too.
Are you telling me
you can make more like him?
No! Not yet.
I sorted out
a few pieces,
but it's not like
I can put together
the same Humpty Dumpty,
if that's what
you're asking.
He was a freak accident!
The goal is to do it better!
So Banner's the only...
(THUDS)
She's an annoying bitch.
Why are you always
hitting people?
(COCKING GUN)
Now what possibly
could I have done to
deserve such aggression?
It's not what you've done.
It's what you're gonna do.
I want what you got
out of Banner.
I want that.
You look like you've got
a little something in you
already, don't you?
I want more.
You've seen what
he becomes, right?
I have.
And it's beautiful.
Godlike.
Well, I want that.
I need that.
Make me that.
I don't know
what you've got
inside you already.
The mix could be
an abomination.
I didn't say
I was unwilling.
I just need
informed consent.
And you've given it.
This is what I was
trying to explain.
(GROWLING)
I don't know what you've
been ladling into yourself.
But clearly it worked.
Let's assume
you don't understand
a word I'm saying,
but if you'll just
get back on the table,
I can fix this.
(ABOMINATION LAUGHING)
SOLDIER 1: Shoot it!
SOLDIER 2: Hey!
No!
(SCREAMING)
Delta 4 to Leader.
They took out
two of our guys,
two of our guys!
Blonsky and the Major
are still inside!
Come on!
Move, move,
move, move!
(ABOMINATION GROWLING)
It's over there!
SOLDIER 2: Drop them!
SOLDIER 3:
What is that thing?
Shoot it!
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
Okay. All right!
You... You, drive!
Let's go! Move, move!
Delta 4 to Leader!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Something big just
went off down here!
General, you should
hear this!
The Hulk is in the street!
I repeat, the Hulk
is in the street!
That's impossible.
You get a hold of yourself,
young man.
You get it together.
What is your position?
121st Street,
heading north
on Broadway!
Turn us around.
We're going back.
Why are we going back?
Damn it!
Give me eyes
down there!
Yes, sir!
What the hell was that?
Go, go, go!
(SIREN WAILING)
No!
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
One of yours?
Oh, my God.
What have you done?
OFFICER: Fire at him,
fire at him!
Do you think a rifle's
gonna hurt that?
Come on!
Sweet.
(ABOMINATION ROARING)
Booyah!
(LAUGHING)
(CAR ALARM BEEPING)
Get out of there, soldier!
Stacy!
Give me a real fight!
SOLDIER 1: Sir?
Sir?
Tell them to bring
everything they've got
and head for Harlem.
It has to be me.
You have to take me
back there.
What are you saying?
You think you can
control it?
No, no, not control it,
but, I don't know,
maybe aim it.
And what if you can't?
We made this thing.
All of us.
Please.
Land us near it.
No, no. No, keep us high.
Open the back door.
Bruce! Bruce, stop!
Stop! What are you doing?
Think about this!
You don't even know
if you'll change!
You don't have to do this!
Please, this is insane!
Betty, I've got to try.
I'm sorry.
Oh, shit!
Get her in here!
Come on, miss.
There. Betty!
(MAN SCREAMING)
(ROARING)
Hulk!
Yeah!
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(CAR ALARM BEEPING)
(LAUGHING)
Come on!
(CHATTERING ON RADIO)
Is that all you've got?
Use that thing, soldier!
Give him some help!
Which one?
Help the green one, damn it!
Which one do you think?
Cut the other one in half!
Ross!
Keep it on him!
Look, I got to
put it down!
Hang on!
(ALARM BEEPING)
BETTY: Dad?
(GROANING)
Are you hurt?
Let me help you.
I'm all right.
Just find a way out.
(LAUGHS)
You don't deserve
this power!
Now watch her die!
Look out!
General?
Any last words?
Hulk smash!
(SCREAMS)
(ROARING)
BETTY: Stop!
It's okay.
Betty.
(SEAGULLS SQUAWKING)
(CAMERA BEEPS)
(HEART BEATING)
(HEART BEATING RAPIDLY)
GENERAL: Reload.
(GROANS)
Reload.
TONY: The smell of stale
beer and defeat.
You know, I hate to say,
"I told you so," General,
but that Super Soldier program
was put on ice for a reason.
I've always felt hardware
was more reliable.
Stark.
General.
You always wear
such nice suits.
Touché.
I hear you have
an unusual problem.
You should talk.
You should listen.
What if I told you
we were putting
a team together?
Who's "we"?